Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/darshan-rawat-2aa95a9b (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Kubernetes

Istio

Continuous Integration and Continuous Delivery (CI/CD)

Languages

English (Full Professional) Hindi (Native or Bilingual)

Certifications

CKA: Certified Kubernetes Administrator

LFS258: Kubernetes Fundamentals

Red Hat Certified System

Administrator in Red Hat OpenStack

Red Hat Certified System Administrator (RHCSA)

Red Hat Certified Engineer (RHCE)

Darshan Rawat

DevOps Engineer at Rakuten Mobile, Inc. Rajasthan

Summary

Working in Rakuten Mobile, Inc. as SRE / DevOps

Experienced in:- OpenShift | Kubernetes | CI / CD | Helm | Istio (Service Mesh) | Docker | Kafka | OpenStack Cloud | Multus CNI | SR-IOV | SDN | Open vSwitch (OVS) | CEPH | shell scripting | Ansible | Jenkins | Linux | Prometheus | Vault | JFrog Artifactory

Having Certificate...

- 1) CKA
- 2) RHCSA in OpenStack
- 3) RHCE
- 4) RHCSA

Experience

Rakuten Mobile, Inc.
DevOps Engineer
March 2021 - Present (1 year)

NEC Corporation India Pvt Ltd.
DevOps Engineer
November 2017 - March 2021 (3 years 5 months)
Japan

Tata Communications Transformation Services (TCTS)
Bsc Engineer
September 2015 - June 2017 (1 year 10 months)

Education

Poornima College Of Engineering
Bachelor of Technology (BTech), Electronics and Communications
Engineering · (2010 - 2014)